https://www.tcs.on.ca/privacy-statement

Affording TCS
Why TCS?
Privacy Statement
The Trinity College School (TCS) website (www.tcs.on.ca) exists to provide the School’s constituents and the general public with information and online services. At TCS, we are committed to protecting the privacy rights of those who use our websites.
Purpose & Types of Information Collected
Website Visitor Information
The Trinity College School public website does not collect personal information (as defined as an individual’s name, address, phone number) without your consent. When you visit the TCS public website, the server automatically collects a limited amount of information via the use of “cookies.” (Cookies are temporary Internet files that are downloaded to your computer or mobile device when you visit a website.) Information collected includes your IP address, the name of your Internet service provider, information concerning your browser and operating system, pages visited, length of time of webpages and geographical information. website visitor information is collected in aggregate form and is not identifiable to an individual visitor. This information is used in connection with the operation and security of the site and to perform statistical analysis of user trends and interests which supports marketing efforts and helps TCS make the site more useful to visitors.
Website Analytics
Our website uses Google Analytics, a service which transmits website traffic data to Google servers in the United States. Google Analytics does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. We use reports provided by Google Analytics to help us understand website traffic and webpage usage. By using this website, you consent to the processing of your data by Google in the manner described in Google's Privacy Policy and for the purposes set out above.
Personal Information
The Trinity College School public website does not collect personal information (as defined as an individual’s name, address, phone number) without your consent. Some functionality of this website may require the provision of personal information (for example, completion of donation forms, submission to the alumni directory, event registration), however, visitors can choose to opt out of such actions. Simply put, we do not collect personal information that identifies an individual unless you voluntarily choose to provide such information.
For individuals attending Trinity College School and their parents, the School collects information as a requirement to fulfill our services. After you have left TCS, we retain this information in order reflect applicable laws and to maintain the School’s relationship with your family. This includes information which is voluntarily provided to the School (whether by digital or other collection tools) and/or acquired from public sources. If you require more information on this policy, please contact the School.
Security & Disclosure of Information
Securing Personal Information
In cases where personal information is voluntarily submitted, TCS will take reasonable steps to protect any personal information you choose to share with the School in a controlled, secure environment. Web forms that request personal and/or sensitive information such as credit card details are built with a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) which enables the secure encrypted transmission of this data.
Disclosure of Information
Any personal information that you provide online will be secured in a password-protected database and will only be accessible to authorized TCS employees unless specifically otherwise stated (for example, in the case of the alumni directory).
Personal information voluntarily submitted through the TCS website is only shared with authorized Trinity College School employees, Trinity College School Foundation members and select volunteers; all such individuals must understand and adhere to the School’s privacy policies.
TCS does not sell or rent any personal information obtained through our website with any other organization or business. In a few limited cases, in the course of regular business operations, TCS may need to provide a contracted third-party entity with basic personal information in order that they may fulfill their contractual obligation. In such cases, only required information is provided and the contracted third-party must adhere to the School’s privacy policy. An example of such a situation would be the provision of constituent name and address information to a mailing house hired to disseminate a TCS publication.
Private website for TCS Community Members
Beyond the public website (www.tcs.on.ca), the School also offers a password-protected site (https://tcs.edsby.com) for TCS community members. Sensitive information such as report cards is secured behind a personal login.
Links to Other Sites
The TCS public website includes links to other organizations’ websites. While we aim to link only to secure sites with appropriate content, please note that TCS is in no way responsible or liable for any external websites.
Opting Out
At any time, should you wish to review or have deleted, personal information that you submitted on the website, please contact communications@tcs.on.ca.
Contact Information
For more information relating to our website privacy statement, please contact the Communications or Information Technology Services department.
Translate
Select LanguageEnglishAmharicBengaliBosnianCebuanoChichewaChinese (Simplified)Chinese (Traditional)CorsicanEsperantoFrenchFrisianGermanGujaratiHausaHawaiianHmongIgboItalianJapaneseJavaneseKannadaKazakhKhmerKurdish (Kurmanji)KyrgyzLaoLatinLuxembourgishMalagasyMalayalamMaoriMarathiMongolianMyanmar (Burmese)NepaliPashtoPunjabiRussianSamoanScottish GaelicSesothoShonaSindhiSinhalaSomaliSpanishSudaneseTajikTamilTeluguTurkishUzbekXhosaYorubaZulu
Media Gallery
Event Calendar
Contact Us
Trinity College School is Canada's energetic, illuminating and complete education for promising students grades 5-12.
This website uses cookies. By continuing to use this website, you consent to our use of these cookies. Find out more.
